Three weeks have passed since that body
swapping business ended.
Nagase made a complete recovery,
so we've been busy making
up for lost time
by working hard on the StuCS paper.
Three weeks ago, I told Nagase
how I felt about her,
and she said that she felt the same way.
But between her injury and
all the work on the paper,
we haven't had a chance to talk alone.
In any case, peace and
quiet had returned to the
Yamaboshi Academy Student
Cultural Society.
Or so we thought,
until school was over the next day.
Here already?
You're always early, Inaba.
I wasn't able to finish up at home.
I have to get this done today.
Are Yui and Aoki around?
I need to check a few things.
I ran into them on the way here.
They'll be late because they're
on monitor duty today.
Don't you find it annoying to
have to wait all the time?
Even if you know it's not their fault.
Well, we can't blame them
if it's not their fault.
Makes you want to take
out your frustration on
whoever happens to be around, right?
Of course not.
What's the point in that?
To feel better by blowing off steam.
You've got a real nasty streak.
I've learned that complaining about
things that only bother you a tiny bit
is actually good stress relief.
Wow.
You're able to reduce your own
stress by taking it out on me...
And yet it doesn't really increase my own.
What's wrong, Inaba?
Inaba?
Wait... What are you doing?
Does your back itch or something?
H-Hey!
Hold on!
What's going on?!
Take off your clothes.
Wh-Why should I take off my clothes?
We have to take off
our clothes to do it.
To do what?!
I know.
You're just toying with
me to relieve stress.
Ow...
I-Inaba!
What are you doing?!
Get off!
Get off! Get off!
Wait! You've got it all wrong!
Really, even I have no idea what's...
Inaba?
Can someone please explain
what the hell is going on?!
Yui?
What's wrong?!
Blood?
Did I do this?
Why?
'Sup!
Whoa! The table!
What happened?! How did it break?!
Wait, Yui. You're bleeding.
Let me see.
Iori!
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
Sorry, I'm going home.
Huh?
What was that all about?
Is it okay to leave it like this?
Are you going out, big brother?
Is something wrong?
Was I about to go outside?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Whoa!
I need to take this call!
Hello? Is this Nagase?
Hey, Taichi! Tell me!
Are we...
Huh?
Um! Er, what...?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
G-Good evening.
Er, yeah...
Good evening.
Sorry!
I'm confused.
I think I called you unconsciously.
I had a feeling that I
needed to talk to you.
A-Actually, I just had a
sudden urge to see you, too.
My body was moving by itself.
You too?
Weird. Something's not right.
Yeah...
Say, you had a feeling that you
needed to talk to me, right?
What did you want to say?
You wanted to talk to me too, right?
Yeah...
Well...
I wanted to talk about the confession!
W-We never had a chance
to clear things up.
Have your...
Have your feelings changed since then?
They haven't.
I still feel the same way I did then.
Really...
So...
Same here.
Um, I feel really
embarrassed right now.
This is definitely embarrassing.
Th-That's enough for today!
Yeah, let's call it a day!
O-Okay, we can do that.
Well, sorry about the weird phone call!
Bye!
Wait, Nagase!
Your girlfriend?
Sh-She's not my girlfriend!
Look at you blush.
But that's good to know.
You were acting weird before.
You're still acting kind of weird,
but at least I know it's
because you're lovesick.
You've got it wrong!
Well, maybe it's better
to leave it at that.
But...
You're so cute, big brother.
Wait, how do you know
what it means to be lovesick?
You need to give your big
brother a proper explanation!
I-Inaba!
About yesterday...
U-Uh...
There's trouble.
Yui and Aoki were taken
into police custody.
Huh?
What?!
I don't know any details,
but the teachers were talking about it.
I tried calling them, but
neither of them are answering.
The cops have them now.
Hold on.
What do you mean?
Why would the police take Aoki
and Kiriyama into custody?
Hell if I know.
Doesn't anyone have more information?
You rang?
Huh?
Fujishima...
Um, I don't think anyone
was talking to you.
Wait, if you know something, tell us.
You shouldn't order people around
when asking for a favor, Inaba-san.
Please tell us what you
know, Fujishima-san.
Yes...
If you let me rent
Nagase-san for two hours,
I'll consider it.
Wha...?
It's a small price to pay.
I'm sure that Nagase-san will
be happy with the deal.
Hey, Fujishima.
That's dirty.
Don't touch her!
There it is again!
What are you trying to do?
What are you doing, Yaegashi-kun?
Dance practice?
Not exactly.
I understand.
If we can find out what
happened to Aoki and Yui,
you can have two or three hours!
So tell us, Fujishima-san.
That was a joke.
I was going to tell you anyway.
What?!
It was a joke?!
My sacrifice was for nothing!
You guys looked way too serious.
I was trying to inject a little humor.
But I didn't think you would
be so mortified by the idea.
This morning, a group of
boys from Akitaka High were
giving some girls from
our school trouble.
Kiriyama-san happened to
pass by and beat them up.
But it sounds like she
used too much force,
so the cops wanted to talk.
That's when Aoki-kun showed
up and went off on them.
"Where are you taking
her? Let her go!"
I hear that he put up a good fight.
Well, she was helping girls
from the same school,
so she should get off with a warning.
Hell yeah!
If they try to punish her,
I'll do whatever it takes to stop them.
How do you know what
happened, Fujishima-san?
My dad happens to be a high-ranking cop.
That's all.
Glad to hear that.
This connection will come in handy.
It won't come free.
Though I can give you a discount.
A conspiracy is born.
This partnership scares me.
So Kiriyama and Aoki
never came to school.
Hey, I've been thinking.
Kiriyama beat up boys from
another school, right?
But she's...
I was also wondering about that.
Yui suffers from androphobia.
She's a lot better now,
but not to the point where she could
grapple with a bunch of boys.
Yet...
You also acted strangely this morning.
Yeah.
Did you hear a voice in your head?
You heard it, too?
Both of you could hear it?
Long time no see, people.
Or maybe it hasn't been that long.
Has it?
Heartseed!
Yes, did you all start hearing
voices in your heads yesterday?
And then your body automatically
does what your mind wants.
Stop messing with us!
We're not your guinea pigs!
Oh, I haven't apologized
to Nagase-san yet.
I would like to say that I'm sorry
from somewhere around
the middle of my heart.
If you're sorry, you
should leave us alone.
No, I'm repeating myself here,
but you people truly fascinate me.
So to explain what's
happening this time,
your deepest desires
have been unleashed.
Our desires have been unleashed?
As I mentioned before,
this phenomena will end when
it's no longer entertaining.
You could say
that I'm helping you
discover your true selves.
True selves...
I have a question.
Is it against the rules to
hide in our rooms?
Huh?
Ah, Inaba-san is very sharp.
All I have to say is
that hiding in your room
could be just as entertaining.
If not, I can make it entertaining.
Make it entertaining...
I'm being a little too generous.
So long then.
So it's Heartseed again.
Sorry about making you worry.
You don't need to apologize.
I wasn't worried about you.
That hurt!
That really hurt, Inaba-chan!
I'm glad that you got
off with a warning.
Yeah, I made out fine...
And Kiriyama's absent again today.
Yui wanted to save those girls
so badly that she beat up the boys.
You wanted to stop the cops
from taking her away
so badly that you put up a struggle.
Under normal circumstances,
you would have shown
self-restraint and stopped.
But your desires were unleashed
and you acted upon them.
That's probably what happened when Yui
broke the table two days ago.
So when Inaba made a move on me...
Stop talking!
You have the sensitivity of a rock!
Do not mention how I disgraced myself.
Hell. Want me to pummel you
until you forget it happened?
Um...
What are you talking about?
See? Look what happened!
Idiot! Moron! Dumbass!
S-Sorry...
It's no big deal.
Two days ago, before you showed up,
my desires were unleashed,
and I kinda put some moves on Taichi.
Oh, really?
But don't get the wrong idea!
This was right after I happened to
come across some dirty pictures.
I-I don't know how far I would have gone.
But it probably wouldn't
have been too far!
I think...
Since I have no experience...
Moving on!
When we were swapping
bodies, we were able
to keep everything amongst ourselves.
But that won't work when
our desires are unleashed.
Yui and Aoki have already used
violence against other people.
Right, outsiders might end up
getting involved this time.
We have two options right now.
The first would be to
suppress your emotions.
The second would be to
just not think about it,
to go wild and have more fun than usual
instead of keeping yourself in check.
What do you mean?
Basically, either you take it easy so
you don't have any dangerous urges,
or you do whatever you want
to avoid any stress build-up.
Both options sound difficult.
That's amazing, Inaban!
You already have a plan!
Sucking up won't do you any good.
It's also important to help each other.
Yeah... That's an option.
Hm? Is it a bad idea?
No, not at all.
It makes sense to help each other.
The rest is up to luck.
We'll just have to play it by ear.
That's all I have to say.
I'm sure Yui will be here tomorrow.
We can continue this discussion then.
Yeah, I don't know what would
be the right thing to do,
but we should be fine
if we work together.
Yup, I just know it.
It's all you, Taichi.
You have to be there for Iori.
Yeah...
But I'll be helping everyone,
not just Nagase.
You only need to worry about Iori.
And Aoki can take care of Yui.
Wait, you're not up to the task.
It's a bad idea to sell me short.
Wait, aren't you coming
to class, Inaban?
I still need to work on the paper.
I'll be there in a bit.
We can help.
It's okay.
Just go away!
I can't get any work done
when you're around.
Bye.
Did I pull it off?
Is everyone else doing okay?
What should I do?
Taichi, can you talk now?
Sure. You usually don't call this late.
Sorry, there's something
I wanted to say.
Picking up where we left off before...
O-Oh, that...
This might not be the best time,
but I think this is important, too.
Can we go status quo for now?
Uh...
Status quo?
I realize that I probably
sound stuck-up,
but I think it's a good idea to
maintain our distance for now.
You know how our desires are
basically out of control now?
Yeah...
I feel like it would be a
bad idea to get closer
under those circumstances.
You're right.
Sorry, I wasn't thinking clearly.
That would be dangerous for us.
Very dangerous.
Who knows what we might do?
Also, I have something to confess.
Confess?
I still lack confidence.
Sometimes, I wonder if
this is really okay.
So I'm a little excited about
having our desires unleashed.
Excited?
My deepest desires will be unleashed.
That may help me discover the real me.
I can't help but look forward to it.
I don't want to be so selfish,
but I can't help myself.
Okay, confession time's over!
Sorry about keeping you up!
I'll buy you lunch or something.
That's the real you talking.
Huh?
The real you is making these
objective observations.
You can discover elements
of the real you in your everyday life.
When you're around, it feels
like everything will be okay.
Bye.
Yeah, bye.
Everything will be okay.
I'll find a way.
I can't screw up this time.
Yahoo!
Cute! Sunny! Strong! Super cute!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't look! I made a huge mistake!
I guess I'm not good enough for you.
How would I know?! Don't ask me!
I'm disappointed, Inaba.
I never thought you would
give up on your friends.